Guide to the George A. Lindbeck Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Collected Materials: Theological Education, Series VII
  - University
    - "Interim Report on Theological Education in University Contexts" by George Lindbeck, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 705)
    - "Interim Report on Theological Education in University Contexts" by George Lindbeck, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 706)
    - "Religion-Social Studies Curriculum Project", 1974 (Box 31, Folder 707)
    - "The Schools of the Minor Professions" by Nathan Glazer in Minerva, v. XII n. 3, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 708)
    - "St. John's" in Change, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 709)
    - "Rooted in the Communities of Faith: A Re-Affirmation of a Learned Ministry" by Krister Stendahl, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 710)
    - "Chapter 17: One Year Later" by James E. Dittes, nd (Box 32, Folder 711)
    - Data, nd (Box 32, Folder 712)
    - "The New Catholic Tuebingen Theology of Walter Kasper: Foundational Issues" by William P. Loewe, Catholic University of America (Box 32, Folder 713)
    - "Some Thoughts Concerning Seminary Curricula" by a member of the Committee on the Pastoral Ministry, nd (Box 32, Folder 714)
    - "St. Andrew's: Change at St. Andrew's" (Box 32, Folder 715)
    - "Theological Education and the University: Goals for the '70s and '80s" (Box 32, Folder 716)
    - "Theological Studies at Harvard Divinity School", nd (Box 32, Folder 717)
    - Untitled, by C. Powers, nd (Box 32, Folder 718)
  - Worship
    - Materials (incl. Evg. Messe nach der lutherischen Agende ) (Box 32, Folder 719)
  - Yale
    - "The Divinity School" by Liston Pope, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 720)
    - "Report of the Divinity School", 1954 (Box 32, Folder 721)
    - "News of Fellows" in The National Council on Religion in Higher Education, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 722)
    - "Topic: Books at Yale" by Reuben A. Holden in Yale Alumni Magazine, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 723)
    - Memos, reports re. Lutheran students at Yale Divinity School, 1970s-1983 (Box 56, Folder 1307)
    - "The Dahl Report" by Robert A. Dahl in Yale Alumni Magazine, v. XXXV n.8, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 724)
    - "A Preliminary Study of a Pecia" in Revue D'Histoire Des Textes, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 725)
    - "The Divinity School and Religious Studies at Yale: An Interim Report" by James T. Laney, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 726)
    - Report of the Committee on the Future of the College and the Graduate School, ca. 1973 (Box 56, Folder 1306)
    - Reports and correspondence re. establishment of doctoral program at Yale Divinity School, and re. relationship between Divinity School and Religious Studies Department at Yale, 1966-1974 (Box 56, Folder 1316)
    - "Theology and Prayer: Some Notes on Seminary Learning" by Don E. Saliers in Reflection, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 727)
    - "A Sense of Urgency: An Interview with Colin Williams" in Yale Alumni Magazine, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 728)
    - "The Present Understanding of Berkeley" by Rowan Greer, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 729)
    - "Disciplined by Theology: A Profile of Paul Holmer" by Mark Horst in Christian Century, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 730)
    - "The New Yale Theology" by Mark I. Wallace in Christian Scholar's Review, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 731)
    - "The Agony of Counterculture" by Kenneth Keniston, nd (Box 32, Folder 732)
    - "The Morality Explosion", nd (Box 32, Folder 733)
    - "Yale Divinity Admissions: A Brief Survey" by Michael Cary, nd (Box 32, Folder 734)
    - "The Young Live Many Lives, Dies Many Deaths" by Arnold Jacob Wolf, nd (Box 32, Folder 735)
    - Miscellaneous, nd (Box 55, Folder 1298)
- Collected Materials: Ecumenism, Series VIII
  - Lutheran
    - re: Accomplie: "L'oeuvre Accomplie les taches a venir" by Herve LeGrand in XXVe Anniversaire du Centre D'Etudes Oecumeniques (Box 33, Folder 736)
    - re: America: "A Social Assessment of the Contemporary American Context" by Karen L. Bloomquist, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 737)
    - re: Art: "A Theology for Artisans of a New Christendom" by Richard John Neuhaus in Commonweal, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 738)
    - re: Augsburg Confession: "A Reply to Robert Goeser" by Michael Root in Dialog, v.30, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 739)
    - re: Augsburg Confession: "New World/Third World/Augsburg Confession", 1979 (Box 33, Folder 740)
    - re: Authority: "The Teaching Ministry of the Whole Church in Lutheran Perspective, with Special Reference to the Authority of Scripture, Tradition, Creeds, Confessions, Bishops, Councils, the Pope", nd (Box 33, Folder 741)
    - re: Bensheim Meeting: "Einheit und Vielfalt in der Neutestamentlichen Lehre von der Kirche" by Ernst Kasemann, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 742)
    - re: Charismatic Movement: "The Charismatic Movement and Lutheran Theology", 1972 (Box 33, Folder 743)
    - re: China: "China Area", 1978 (Box 33, Folder 744)
    - re: Christenheit: "Nachtigall in den Waldern der Christenheit?" (Box 33, Folder 745)
    - re: Church: "Religious Belief and Experience: A Preliminary Report of Findings from the 7th Lutheran Listening Post Questionnaire" by Robert Wuthnow, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 746)
    - re: Confessions: "The Doctrine of the Church in the Lutheran Confessions: Essay Adopted by the Commissioners of the American Lutheran Church and the Lutheran Church-Missouri Synod", 1972 (Box 33, Folder 747)
    - re: Convocation of Teaching Theologians: "Lutheran Identity in the 1990s: Constructive Proposals", 1992 (Box 33, Folder 748)
    - re: Creation: "Critique of Klalter J. Kukkonen's "The Word of Creation and the Word of Redemption" by Carl E. Braaten in Commission on the Comprehensive Study of the Doctrine of the Ministry (Box 33, Folder 749)
    - re: Crisis: "The Continuing Crisis" in Forum Letter, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 750)
    - re: Crisis: "Mythic and Ritual Resources for the Current Crisis in American Praxis" by Philip Hefner, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 751)
    - re: Crisis: "Assails Synod's Crisis" by James E. Adams, nd (Box 33, Folder 752)
    - re: Cross: "The Word of the Cross" by Leo J. Donovan in Chicago Studies, v.25, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 753)
    - re: Culture: "Culture Wars: Should Lutherans Volunteer or Be Conscripted?" by Ted Peters in ELCA Lectures, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 754)
    - re: Depression: "American Lutherans and the Depression of the 1930s: Observations and Questions for Conversation" by Todd Nichol, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 755)
    - re: Dialogue: "A Decade of Dialogue: An Assessment of U.S.A. Lutheran Conversations with Reformed, Anglican, and Roman Catholic Theologians" by Carl E. Braaten (Box 33, Folder 756)
    - re: Dialogue: "Dialogue with Reformed", nd (Box 33, Folder 757)
    - re: Dialogue: "The Lord's Supper in the Dialogues: A Horizontal Look" by Edward H. Schroede, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 758)
    - re: Dialogue: "Discussion Summary", nd (Box 33, Folder 759)
    - re: Dialogue: "Der LWB als Partner im Dialog mit Anderen Kirchen, unter besonderer Berucksichtigung des Verstandnisses des LWB als Ausdruck und Instrument der 'lutherischen Gemeinschaft'" by F. O. Scharbau (Box 33, Folder 760)
    - re: Diskussionprotokoll: "Luthertum und okumenische Bewegung II" (Box 33, Folder 761)
    - re: Doctrine: "What is a Doctrine?" by R. Bohlmann, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 762)
    - re: Dogma: "Christian Tradition: A History of the Development of Doctrine: Reformation of Church and Dogma" by Jaroslav Pelikan, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 763)
    - re: ELCA: "Gospel and Ministry in the ELCA" by Paul R. Hinlicky in Lutheran Quarterly (Box 33, Folder 763)
    - re: ELCA: "The ELCA Sex Report" in Lutheran Commentator, v.5 n.5, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 765)
    - re: ECLA: "Task Force on the Study of Ministry", 1991 (Box 33, Folder 766)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Ecumenism: A Lutheran Commitment: An Official Statement of the Lutheran Church in America", 1982 (Box 33, Folder 767)
    - re: Ecumenism: "An Anglican Perspective on the Ecumenical Work of the Lutheran Churches" by Stephen Sykes, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 768)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Ecumenical Directions" by Burgess, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 769)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Ecumenical Reception in the Lutheran Churches" by Samuel Nafzger, nd (Box 33, Folder 770)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Ecumenical Reception in the Lutheran Churches: The North American Experience" by William G. Rusch, nd (Box 33, Folder 771)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Lutheran Churches in the Ecumenical Movement", 1977 (Box 33, Folder 772)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Lutheran Ecumenical Identity: Unity in Reconciled Diversity" by David W. Preus, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 773)
    - re: Ecumenism: "The Lutheran Ecumenical Task from an African Perspective" by Hirpo, nd (Box 33, Folder 774)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Lutheran Ecumenism: Relevance, Priorities" by Anna-Marie Aagaard, nd (Box 33, Folder 775)
    - re: Ecumenism: "New Paths in Lutheran Ecumenism" by Bishop M. Buthelezi, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 776)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Okumenische Rezeption in den Lutherischen Kirchen" by Kate Mahn (Box 33, Folder 777)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Die Wirkungen des Instituts und seine Zukunftigen Aufgaben aus der sicht Okumenischer Forschung und Dialoge" by D. Georg Kretschmar (Box 33, Folder 778)
    - re: Ecumenism: "Erwagungen uber 'Die Wirkungen des Institutes und seine Zukunftige aufgaben Geschichte'" (Box 33, Folder 779)
    - re: Faith: "Church and Society Address: 'A Call to Faithfulness Conference'" by L. Rasmussen, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 780)
    - re: Family: "A Lutheran Practical Theology for the Family", 1992 (Box 33, Folder 781)
    - re: Foreign Relations: "Theological Consensus and Experienced Fellowship: A Reaction to Dr. Walter Altmann's Paper" by Arve Brunvell (Box 33, Folder 782)
    - re: Hartford: "The Hartford Appeal: A Symposium" by Harvey Cox in Worldview, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 783)
    - re: Heretics: "The New Heretics" by Susan Cheever Cowley and Laurie Lisle in Newsweek, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 784)
    - re: Infallibility: "Lutheran Musings on the Psycho-Social Sitz im Leben of Papal Infallibility" by Fred Kramer; "Infallibility Language and the Early Lutheran Tradition" by Gerhard O. Forde (Box 33, Folder 785)
    - re: Justification by Faith: "Justification Today: Studies and Reports" in Lutheran World; "Usus Legis:The Functional Understanding of Law in Lutheran Theology" by Gerhard O. Forde in Princeton; "Rewards, But in a Very Different Sense" by Joseph A. Burgess; "Justification in the Late Middle Ages" by Freelich, 1965; 1979; 1981; 1982 (Box 34, Folder 786)
    - re: Justification by Faith: "Justification Was Topic of Earlier Discussions" in Lutheran World Information, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 787)
    - re: Justification by Faith: "Rechtfertigung und Anthropologie" by Wenzel Lohff; "Forensic Justification and the Christian Life: Triumph or Tragedy?" by Gerhard O. Forde; "Recent Lutheran Theologies on Justification by Faith: A Sampling" by Bertram (Box 34, Folder 788)
    - re: Justification by Faith: "Examination of the USA Lutheran Bilaterals on 'Justification'" by Carl E. Braaten, nd (Box 34, Folder 789)
    - re: Konsultation: "Konsultation Klingenthal", 1990 (Box 34, Folder 790)
    - re: Konsultation: "Zukunftige Schwerpunkte okumenischer Forschung" by Eeva Martikainen, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 791)
    - re: Konsultation: "Zukunftige Okumenischer Forschung" by Martin N. Dreher, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 792)
    - re: Konsultation: "Zukunftige Schwerpunkte okumenischer Forschung" by Marc Lienhard, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 793)
    - re: Kuratoriums: "Protokoll der Sitzung des Kuratoriums der Lutherischen Stiftung fur okumenische Forschung", 1964 (Box 34, Folder 794)
    - re: Law: "Lutherans and the Problem of Law and Gospel" by David Granskou (Box 34, Folder 795)
    - re: Law: "To Serve the Lord of All: Law, Gospel, and Social Responsibility" by Richard John Neuhaus, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 796)
    - re: Lonergan: "Ongoing Collaboration: The First International Lonergan Congress", 1970 (Box 34, Folder 797)
    - re: Lonergan: "Ongoing Collaboration: The First International Lonergan Congress", 1970 (Box 34, Folder 798)
    - re: Luther: "The Enduring Relevance of Martin Luther 500 Years After His Birth" by Jaroslav Pelikan in New York Times Magazine; "Luther in Perspective" by Carter Lindberg in LCA Partners, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 799)
    - re: Luther: "Demut, Glaube und Rechtfertigung in Luthers Romerbrief-Vorlesung" by Ernst Bizer, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 800)
    - re: Lutheranism: "Who Do You Say That I Am?" by Linda-Marie Delloff in The Lutheran, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 801)
    - re: Lutheranism: "Chilstrom to Council: Avoid Federation" in The Lutheran, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 802)
    - re: Lutheran Ministry: "Readiness for Ministry: Lutheran Clusters", 1976 (Box 34, Folder 803)
    - re: Lutheran Research: "Draft: Descriptio of Lutheran Foundation for Interconfessional Research" by V. Vajta, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 804)
    - re: Lutheran Research: "Work of the Commission on Inter-Confessional Research", nd (Box 34, Folder 805)
    - re: Lutheran Research: "Proposed By-Laws to the Constitution of the Lutheran Foundation for Inter-Confessional Research" (Box 34, Folder 806)
    - re: Lutheran Research: "Constitution of Lutheran Foundation for Inter-Confessional Research" (Box 34, Folder 807)
    - re: Lutheran Research: "Suggested Topics for Future Research Program of the Foundation" by George Lindbeck, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 808)
    - re: Lutheran Research: "Lutheran Foundation for Inter-Confessional Research: Contributions and Expenses 1963 for Operating", 1964 (Box 34, Folder 809)
    - re: Lutheran Research: "The Development of Interconfessional Research" by Paul Minear, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 810)
    - re: Lutheran Research: "Circular Letter of Lutheran Foundation for Inter-Confessional Research", 1964 (Box 34, Folder 811)
    - re: Lutheran Writings: "In Brief" by Thelma Megill-Cobbler in Lutheran Partners, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 812)
    - re: Lutherans at Yale: "The Lutherans at Yale: Six Luthern Faculty Members and Nearby Bethesda Church Give This University's Seminary a Lutheran Flavor" by Gregory L. Jackson and Rebecca Wenger in The Lutheran, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 813)
    - re: Lutherische Weltbund Theologische Kommission: "Die soteriologischen Motive der altkirchlichen Glaubensbekenntnisse" by Ernst Kinder, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 814)
    - re: Lutherische Weltbund:" Dokument Nr. 79", 1963 (Box 34, Folder 815)
    - re: Methodology: "International Consultation on Ecumenical Methodology", 1976 (Box 34, Folder 816)
    - re: Ministry: "Ordained Minister and Layman in Lutheranism" by John Reumann (Box 34, Folder 817)
    - re: Ministry: "Introducing the Study for Ministry" by Joseph M. Wagner in Study of Ministry Report, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 818)
    - re: Ministry: "Ministry Fall Hearing Dates, Procedures Set by ECLA" in Study of Ministry Report, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 819)
    - re: Ministry: "The Ministry of the Word of God: One Divine Office in Various Human Forms" by William H. Lazareth, nd (Box 34, Folder 820)
    - re: Mission: "The Mission of the Gospel: The God of the Gospel and Our Humanity" by Paul R. Sponheim, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 821)
    - re: Mission: "The Mission of the Gospel to the Nations" by Carl E. Braaten, nd (Box 34, Folder 822)
    - re: Missouri Synod: "Missouri's Inner Struggle" by Martin E. Marty in The Lutheran; "The Missouri-Synod Lutheran Civil War" by Kenneth L. Woodward in Christian Herald Magazine, 1972; 1970 (Box 34, Folder 823)
    - re: Purgatory: "The Fathers and the Cleansing Fire" by Robert B. Eno (Box 34, Folder 824)
    - re: Rahner: "A Final Harvest: Karl Rahner's Last Theological Writings" by Leo J. O'Donovan in Religious Studies Review, v.11 n.4, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 825)
    - re: Rahner: "A Journey into Time: The Legacy of Karl Rahner's Last Years" by Leo J. O'Donovan in Theological Studies, v.46, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 826)
    - re: Saints: "New York Lutheran Center", 1982 (Box 34, Folder 827)
    - re: Scriptures: "Scriptures and Confessions: A Session with Schneeweiss" by Robert W. Bertram (Box 34, Folder 828)
    - re: Scriptures: "Study Edition of A Statement of Scriptural and Confessional Principles", 1972 (Box 34, Folder 829)
    - re: Socialism: "Church in Socialism: An Attempt to Contextualize Lutheran Theology in the German Democratic Republic" by Michael F. Moller (Box 34, Folder 830)
    - re: Theology: "Sonderdruck aus Christliche Freiheit: im Dienst am Menschen", 1972 (Box 34, Folder 831)
    - re: University: "The Future Role of the Universities in the Education for Religious Ministries", nd (Box 34, Folder 832)
    - re: War: "Toward a World Without Weapons" by J. Bryan Hehir in America, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 833)
    - re: War: "War-Nation-Church Study Group", 1978 (Box 34, Folder 834)
    - re: War: "War-Nation-Church Study Group Members", 1978 (Box 34, Folder 835)
    - re: Widerspruch: "Widerspruch, Dialog und Einigung" by Bernhard Lohse, Wolf-Dieter Hauschild, Wenzel Lohff, Adolf Sperl, Walter Sparn, Friedrich Hubner, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 836)
  - Intra-Lutheran
    - Forum Letter, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 837)
    - Forum Letter, 1988-1989 (Box 56, Folder 1309)
    - Forum Letter, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 838)
    - Forum Letter, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 839-841)
    - Forum Letter, nd (Box 35, Folder 842)
    - The Lutheran Listening Post: Clergy-Weighted, nd (Box 35, Folder 843)
    - The Lutheran Listening Post: Laity-Weighted, nd (Box 35, Folder 844)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): News Service, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 845)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Protokoll der Konfessionskundlichen Tagung Lutherischer Theologen in Hoisbuettel, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 846)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Commission Theology, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 847)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Osnabruck Conference: Papers, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 848)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Osnabruck Conference: Commission on Theology Agenda, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 849)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Executive Committee Meeting, Geneva, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 850)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Fourth Assembly Work Book, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 851)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Kommission fur interkonfessionelle Forschung, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 852)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Vatican II, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 853)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF)/Lutheran Weltbund, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 854)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Tokyo Conference: Ecumenical Situation and Commitment of Lutheranhism in Asia and Africa, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 855)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 856)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): An Appeal for Theological Affirmation, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 857)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): "Finding God and the Hartford Appeal" by Avery Dulles, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 858)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Hartford Affirmation: Limiting Liberal Theology, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 859)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): The Hartford Appeal: A Symposium, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 860)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): A Pilgrim Piece of Time and Space, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 861)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Readers' Response: On Attacking the Relevant Reverends, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 862)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Report of the Consultation on the Ecumenical Orientation and Work of the LWF, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 863)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Worship Among Lutherans, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 1310)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Self-Understanding and Ecumenical Role of the Lutheran World Federation, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 1310)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Growth in Ecumenical Commitment, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 1310)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Seventh Assembly Materials, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 864)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Recommendations to the Commission for a New Lutheran Church from the Joint AELC-ALC-LCA Conference of Bishops, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 865)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Aide Memoire: Venice Consultation on LWF Dialogues, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 866)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Constitution of the Lutheran World Federation, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 867)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Preamble, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 868)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Monthly, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 869)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Confessional Research, nd (Box 36, Folder 870)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Geneva Conference: Documentation on the Current Interconfessional Conversations of the LWF, nd (Box 36, Folder 871)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): "The Hartford Appeal and Ecumenism" by Avery Dulles (Box 36, Folder 872)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Hartford and Evangelicalism (Box 36, Folder 873)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Reports and Articles (Box 36, Folder 874)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): Source Materials, nd (Box 36, Folder 875)
    - Lutheran World Federation (LWF): The Work of the Institute for Ecumenical Research: Past Fruits and Future Tasks, LWF Perspective (Box 36, Folder 876)
  - Lutheran-Catholic Dialogue
    - re: Accord: "Lutheran-Catholic Accord Voted" by Edward B. Fiske in New York Times, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 877)
    - re: Action: "Blueprints for Action", 1966 (Box 36, Folder 878)
    - re: Apostolic Succession: "Recognition of a Presbyterial Succession?" by Harry J. McSorley, nd (Box 36, Folder 879)
    - re: Augsburg Confession: "Dialog-Zeichen aus Augsburg" in Augsburger Allgemeine, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 880)
    - re: Augsburg Confession: "Jesuit Brakes Runaway Push for Augsburg Confession" in Our Sunday Visitor, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 881)
    - re: Augsburg Confession: "The Augsburg Confession and the Catholic Tradition" by Robert L. Wilken in Advent; "An Exegesis of the Apology of the Augsburg Confession, Article IV" by Robert W. Jenson; "Confessio Augustana-Bekenntnis des einen Glaubens", 1980; nd (Box 36, Folder 882)
    - re: Augsburg Confession: "Vorlage fur eine gemeinsame lutherisch-katholische Interpretation der Rechtfertigungslehre der CA"; "Anmerkungen zur Frage einer 'Anerkennung' der Confessio Augustana durch die katholische Kirche" by Joseph Kardinal Ratzinger in Munchener Theologische Zeitschrift; "Das Tridentinische und die Nachtridentinischen Bekenntnisse der Rom-Kath. Kirche und die Confessio Augustana" by Vinzenz Pfnur in Studien zur Bekenntnisbildung, nd; 1978; 1980 (Box 36, Folder 883)
    - re: Augsburg Confession: "Die Confessio August im Lichte des Gegenwartigen Dialogs" by Vilmos Vajta in Kirche des Evangeliums (Box 36, Folder 884)
    - re: Confessio Augustana: "Suggestions for the Confessio Augustana Publication" by George Lindbeck, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 885)
    - re: Augustana Confession: "Die Confessio Augustana als anfrage an lutheraner und katholiken im 16. Jahrhundert und Heute" by Erwin Iserloh in Sonderdruck aus Catholica, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 886)
    - re: Augustana Confession: untitled, nd (Box 36, Folder 887)
    - re: Breach: "An Exchange of Letters on 'Healing the Breach'" by Paul Meyer and Richart Neuhaus in Lutheran Forum, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 888)
    - re: Breach: "Toward Healing the Breach: Lutherans and Catholics in Dialogue", 1980 (Box 36, Folder 889)
    - re: Breach: "Toward Healing the Breach: Lutherans and Catholics in Dialogue", 1990 (Box 36, Folder 890)
    - Christ: "Lutherans Told Unity Means 'Back to Christ,' Not Back to Rome" in National Lutheran, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 891)
    - re: Christ: "One Jesus, Many Christs?" by Don Cupitt, nd (Box 36, Folder 892)
    - re: Church: "The Russian Orthodox Church" by Harold J. Berman in Christianity and Crisis, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 893)
    - re: Church: "Submitting to CPH Lindbeck, Elliot Papers Delivered at Institute on Church's Mission" in CPH Commentator, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 894)